morningfalls.com 2009-11-24

# Morning Falls - Performance Based Display Network

PRIVACY POLICY 

Morning Falls produced this privacy policy in to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of the Morning Falls Online Display Network. 

**Cookies  
**A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

The Morning Falls Online Display Network uses cookies for the purposes of tracking when an Internet user has seen an advertisement. These cookies do not and will not provide Morning Falls with any Personally Identifiable information. Instead, these cookies are used for various reasons including to inform the Morning Falls Online Display Network if an advertisement has been served to the same computer before, and if so, when the advertisement was served. 

**Opt-Out  
**Internet users have the option to block the use of cookies by changing an Internet browser setting. In addition, users have the option to block the use of JavaScript, which is used by the Morning Falls Online Display Network to display advertisements. For more information, please see the documentation regarding your Internet browser. 

We will send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We also communicate with user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to the account via e-mail or telephone when requested.

**Collection and Use of Non-Personally Identifiable Information  
**All information shared with both advertisers and publishers within the Morning Falls Online Display Network is done so in an aggregate fashion. This allows us to provide members of the advertising network with broad percentages regarding the users who are receiving advertisements through the network. However, this data is not linked to any form of Personally Identifiable information. 

Information collected by advertisers on their websites who are members of the Morning Falls Online Display Network may contain Personally Identifiable information. However, data such as this is provided by the individual Internet user in the form of online order forms, contests, or otherwise through the members website, not morningfalls.com. This Personally Identifiable information collected outside the Morning Falls Online Display Network is subject to the privacy policies of the individual advertisers involved. 

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Collection and Use of Personally Identifiable Information  
**Registering to become a member of the Morning Falls online advertising network, either as an advertiser or a publisher, requires the submission of Personally Identifiable information to our company. This can include your full name, mailing and/or billing address, email address, company name, and website URL. We use this information to service your accounts and respond to inquiries. Communications to our business users are related to the Advertising Network. We hold all such information submitted in strict confidence. Under no circumstances will a user's email address, mailing address, phone number, or other Personally Identifiable information be sold to, supplied to, or otherwise made available to any third party. For registered members to update or correct their personal information reach us through the "Contact Us" page. 

**Security** **  
** We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.   
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy  
**Morning Falls may find it necessary to update this Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted at this site. Except as otherwise required by law, any modifications made to this Privacy Policy will not materially affect the privacy of data collected by Morning Falls prior to the effective date of the policy change. 

Please direct any questions regarding our privacy policy to our office via mail (listed below), or via email.

**Morning Falls LLC**  
3440 Youngfield St. #244  
Wheat Ridge, CO 80033
